







Senior Manager seeking roles in Project Management, Program Management, Service Delivery Management, Strategic Planning, Process Improvement, Resource Optimization, Stakeholder Management, Technology Management, Client Management, SQL, Java, Linux, Power BI



Total Experience: 15 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Designation: Senior Manager - IT

Current Company: Mindtree Pvt. Ltd

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Role: Program Mgr

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Senior Manager,Program Manager,Project Management,Program Management,Service Delivery Management,Strategic Planning,Process Improvement,Resource Optimization,Stakeholder Management,Technology Management,Client Management,SQL,Java,Linux,Power BI

Verified : Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21

Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

PMP, ITIL and Prince2 Certified and High-caliber IT professional with over 15 years of rich and extensive experience including over 7 years of onsite experience in Singapore as a Production Support Manager

Domain exposure entails Prime Brokerage, Equity Finance, Investment banking, Application Support & Infrastructure Keen analyst with excellence in gathering and understanding requirements of clients & other multiple stakeholders (at strategic and tactical levels), followed by translation into functional specifications

Proven Excellence in managing service delivery frameworks; developing relationships with business stakeholders and leadership teams across geographies and departments

Success in leading end-to-end perfection across Service Design, Operations, Transition & Project Management with excellence in managing issues that could impact end-to-end delivery operations, performing root-cause analysis for remedying technical difficulties and providing leadership/direction

Work Experience

- Mindtree Pvt. Ltd as Senior Manager IT May 2017 to Till Date
- Cognizant Technology Solutions as Manager Apr 2012 to May 2017
- Dell Perot Systems as Senior Associate Sep 2007 to Apr 2012

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Arulmigu Meenakshi Amman College of Engineering, Namandi in 2004

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version Last Used Experience |
|-------------|------------------------------|
| SQL, PL/SQL | |

Important

Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

| Oracle 10g, SQL Server | | |
|---|------|----------------------|
| UNIX, LINUX, WINDOWS XP | | |
| Windows 7, MAC | | |
| Service Now, ITSM, SCOM | | |
| Sitescope, Powershell, Netcool, Autosys | | |
| ETL Informatica, Power BI, Azure Portal | | |
| JAVA | | |
| Shell Scripting | | |
| AZURE | 2020 | 3 Year(s) 8 Month(s) |

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| Tamil | Proficient | | | ✓ |
| Hindi | Proficient | ✓ | ✓ | ✓ |
| English | Expert | ✓ | ✓ | ✓ |

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.